Guide to the Edwin "Bud" Shrake Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Screenplays/Teleplays, 1971-2002, undated
  - Screenplays/Teleplays – Unproduced, 1973-2001, undated
    - Pancho Villa Projects: Pancho, Billy & Esmerelda (a.k.a. Too Young To Die), 1990-2001, undated
      - Notes, research, outline, draft photocopy (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Draft printout photocopies (2), March 11, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Corrected shooting script printout, April 21, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Draft printout photocopy, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Draft printout, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Feature Film Investment Proposals (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Prairie Pirates, 1988-1989, undated
      - Correspondence, notes, research, recordings (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Printout fax photocopy (First Draft), September 7, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Printout with inserts, correspondence, notes, clippings (first draft) (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Corrected printout photocopy (first draft) (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Royo County, 1974-1992, undated
      - Typescript photocopy (First Draft), January 25, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Typescript photocopy, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Typescript photocopy and correspondence, January 27, 1992, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Skeleton Dance, undated
      - Corrected typescript (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Slim and None, 1981-1985
      - Legal agreements (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Scenario typescript, September 1981 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Two scenario typescript photocopies with notes, inserts, November 1981 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Notes, clippings, research, treatments, correspondence (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Corrected treatment typescript and photocopy, June 8, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Corrected typescript, July 4, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy, July 4, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Typescript photocopy, August 1, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Typescript photocopy with correspondence, August 16, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Corrected composite photocopy, circa 1982 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Corrected composite typescript fragment, circa 1982 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Corrected composite typescript, February 1983 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Corrected composite typescript, March 1983 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Printout photocopy with correspondence and notes, March 1983 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Typescript photocopy (Third Draft), March 11, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Treatment, October 2, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Draft printout, January 1985 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Corrected printout photocopy, January 1985 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Inscribed printout, May 1985 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Strange Peaches, 1973-1998
      - Notes, clippings (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Corrected composite typescript, circa March 1973 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Corrected typescript, March 5, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy, March 5, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Typescript photocopy, November 9, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Chartoff Productions agreements, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Inscribed printout, April 1981 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Draft typescript, April 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - CCorrected typescrip, April 8, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Two inscribed printout photocopies, April 8, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - The Texas Devils, 1979, undated
      - Treatment, undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Corrected typescript (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy with three inscribed cover pages (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - The Thrill of Charlie and the Agony of Bernice, 1982-1983
      - Notes, correspondence, clippings (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Notes, clippings, research (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Notes, photocopies of scenario, clippings, correspondence, screenplay (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Proposed agreement (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Yarbee, undated
      - Two corrected typescript photocopies (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Zebras, 1989-1991, undated
      - Correspondence, agreements (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Corrected typescript, incomplete (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - "First Draft" printout and inscribed photocopy (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Unwritten screenplay/teleplay projects, 1981-1993, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Play Scripts, 1977-2010, undated
  Again, this series is divided into Produced and Unproduced material.
  The sub-series of produced works is arranged by production date. The bulk of the sub-series consists of Pancho Villa's Wedding Day, which, after Shrake turned it from a film script into a play script, underwent more incarnations, including as a musical. Numerous, corrected drafts are included, from 1977 to 1994, when he stopped revising it. The play was staged in 1984. The last play in the series, The Friend of Carlos Monzon, was staged posthumously, and materials from that production, though not directly donated by Shrake, are included.
  The Unproduced sub-series contains only one untitled playscript,and notes, correspondence, research and a corrected draft for "Jack," a play Shrake co-wrote with Michael Rudman, but failed to get produced.
  - Pancho Villa's Wedding Day, 1977-1994, undated
    - "First Draft" typescript photocopy (67 pages), June 1977 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - "First Draft" corrected typescript (88 pages), June 1977 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - "First Draft" typescript (99 pages), June 1977 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Bound typescript with clipping, correspondence, circa 1978 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript draft with inserts and notes, November 1980 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Notes (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Research (Box 70, Folder 7, Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Pancho Villa – Draft typescript and photocopy, February 1981 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Corrected typescript (104 pages), July 1981 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Corrected typescript photocopy (104 pages), July 1981 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Typescript photocopy (70 pages), July 1981 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Musical Version: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Musical Version: Notes, cover pages, song lyrics, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Musical Version: Corrected typescript photocopy, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Musical Version: Typescript photocopy with three inscribed cover pages, 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript, August 1981 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Production Contract (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - "Revision to take out music" printout, July 1983 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Corrected printout photocopy with note, July 1983 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Corrected printout photocopy, signed drawing on cover, July 1983 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Press and marketing (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Two programs – one inscribed and signed (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Financial (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Corrected printout photocopy with insert, February 1984 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Corrected printout photocopy, signed drawing on cover, February 1984 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Corrected printout photocopy, circa February 1984 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - "Post production revision" printout, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Pancho and Ambrose: Corrected printout, March 7, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Pancho and Ambrose: Printout, March 15, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Pancho and Ambrose: Corrected printout photocopy, August 1, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Pancho and Ambrose: Printout, August 1, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Pancho and Ambrose: Signed and annotated printout photocopy, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Revision printout pages, September 17, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Corrected printout with inserts, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Printout photocopy, January 1985 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Composite printout, January 1985 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Pancho and the Old Gringo – printout, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Corrected printout photocopy with inserts, undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Printout photocopy (77 pages), undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Pancho Villa's Wedding – inscribed printout photocopy (68 pages), undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Printout photocopy (104 pages), undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Printout photocopy (119 pages), undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Benchmark, 1999-2007, undated
    - Correspondence, revisions (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Corrected printout, March 21, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Printout, March 21, 2000 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Signed program, photocopied pages (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Corrected printout, February 2007 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Signed program pages of other plays (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - The Friend of Carlos Monzon, 2005-2010, undated
    - "First Draft" printout, November 22, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Corrected and annotated "First Draft" printout, November 22, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Corrected and annotated printout, May 10, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Printout draft, August 2008 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Invitation list, invitation text, and invitation (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Two programs (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - General (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Unproduced Play Scripts, 2003-2009, undated
    - Untitled [play] script (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Jack
      - Notes, correspondence, invoice, research (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Corrected printout photocopy (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Non-Fiction, 1948-2002, undated
  Scope and Contents
  Though essentially consisting of only three projects, all published, this sub-series contains a voluminous amount of research on its subjects, especially Willie Nelson. Included in the Willie materials are numerous tapes and transcripts of interviews Shrake and others did with Nelson and his acquaintances. Also included are clipping files on Nelson and country music going back to 1978 (when Shrake was writing the Songwriter screenplay), and many files of corrected draft fragments. Notably, the opposite is true for the Barry Switzer book, Bootlegger's Boy—no research files are present in the papers, except for some clippings on Switzer gathered post-publication. The sub-series Harvey Penick Books contains drafts for all five Penick/Shrake books, plus research on Penick and golf, interviews, contracts, photographs, and all kinds of marketing materials. As with the files on Willie Nelson, the Harvey Penick files are ample with biographical information on their subject and insight into their subject's craft.
  - Willie, 1978-2002, undated
    - Contract file (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1978-1986 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - General research (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - McCall notes and memos (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Clippings and interviews from Cheryl McCall (Box 77, Folder 5-8, Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Notes (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Songbook photocopies (4) and note (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Song lyrics (photocopies) (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Timelines (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Travel notes (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Outline of book about Willie by Scobey (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 1988-1989, undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Interview questions and notes (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Interview discs and paperwork (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Interview transcripts
      - Sammy Allred (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 1)
      - James "Kimo" Alo (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 2)
      - David Amram (Box 79, Box 3)
      - Chet Atkins, Tape #4 (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 4)
      - Bennie Binyon (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 5)
      - Rick Blackburn (Box 79, Box 6)
      - Pat Butler (Box 79, Box 7)
      - Don Cherry (Box 79, Box 8)
      - Biff Collie and Mae Axton (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 9)
      - Billy Cooper (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 10)
      - Erma Reed Duffy (Box 79, Box 11)
      - Diane Echenbaum (Box 79, Box 12)
      - Paul English (Box 79, Box 13)
      - Tompall Glaser (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 14)
      - Tom Gresham (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 15)
      - Joel Katz (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 16)
      - Sheryl Leverett (2 copies) (Box 79, Box 17)
      - James (Podie) Locke (2 copies) (Box 80, Box 1)
      - Cheryl McCall (2 copies) (Box 80, Box 2)
      - Gates Moore (2 copies) (Box 80, Box 3)
      - Lana Nelson (Box 80, Box 4)
      - Shirley Nelson (2 copies) (Box 80, Box 5)
      - Willlie Nelson (2 copies), 1975 (Box 80, Box 6)
      - Willie and Bobbi Nelson, March 1987 (Box 80, Box 7)
      - Willie and Bobbi Nelson (second copy), March 1987 (Box 80, Box 8)
      - Willie Nelson, March 19, 1987 (Box 80, Box 9)
      - Willie Nelson (2 copies), March 23-24, 1987 (Box 80, Box 10)
      - Willie Nelson, Tape 1-3, September 17, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Willie Nelson Tape 1-3 (second copy), September 17, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Willie Nelson Tape 4-6, September 17, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Willie Nelson Tape 4-6 (second copy), September 17, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Willie Nelson (2 copies), February 23, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Frank and Jeanne Oakley (2 copies) (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Sydney Pollack (2 copies) (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Dudley Prewitt (2 copies) (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Rattlesnake Annie (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Mark Rothbaum (2 interviews; 2 copies each) (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Susan Rossman (2 copies) (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Darrell Royal (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Tim O'Connor (2 copies) (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Martha Scott (2 interviews; 2 copies each) (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - W.B. Shelton (2 copies; second incomplete) (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Hazel Smith (2 copies) (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Mike Tollison (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Larry Trader (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Zeke Varnon (2 copies) (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Billy Walker (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Jim Wiatt (2 copies) (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Charlie Williams (2 copies) (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Bill Wittliff (2 copies) (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Sybil Greenhaw Young (2 copies) (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Various (Mildred, Willie, Bobbie) (2 copies) (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Various (Willie, Waylon, Neal, Marvin, Bud) (2 copies each; incomplete) (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Book outline and synopsis (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Expenses (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Corrected typescript fragments with inserts (Box 82, Folder 14, Box 83, Box 84, Box 85)
    - "The Untitled Willie Nelson Book," inscribed (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
    - "First full-length m.s." printout, inscribed (Box 86, Folder 3-6, Box 87, Folder 1)
    - "First full-length m.s." printout copy, inscribed (Box 87, Folder 2-6)
    - Editing notes, epilogue and prologue printouts (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Corrected printout copy (Box 87, Folder 8, Box 88, Folder 1-3)
    - Corrected galley proof copy (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Audio script (2 copies), with correspondence (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Publicity (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Reviews (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Esther Newberg correspondence and clippings (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Royalty Statements (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Interview audio cassettes and mini-cassettes #1-38: Allred, Alo, Amram, Atkins, Binion, Blackburn, L. Butler, P. Butler, Cherry, Collie/Axton, Cooper, Eichenbaum (3), English, Glaser, Gresham, Hunter, Katz, Leverett, Locke, Lunde, McCall, Moore, B. Nelson (2), L. Nelson, S. Nelson, W. Nelson (10) (Box 89)
    - Interview audio cassettes and mini-cassettes #39-64: W. Nelson (2), F. & J. Oakley, O'Connor, Pollack, Prewitt, Rattlesnake Annie, Rossman, Rothbaum, Royal, Scott (3), Varnon (2), Walker, Wiatt, Wilcox, Williams, Wittliff, Young; "Willie on PBS Nov. 14, 1988"; "Jug Fishing 4-87" (Box 90)
  - Bootlegger's Boy, 1989-1997, undated
    - "Unedited version" printout, inscribed (Box 91, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Corrected printout photocopy (Box 91, Folder 6-7, Box 92, Folder 1-2)
    - Corrected printout, chapter 34 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Corrected galley proof photocopies (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Dust jacket and marketing text (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - William Morrow catalog, autographed (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Switzer file (clippings, notes, invitation) (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Harvey Penick Books, 1948-2001, undated
    - Little Red Book, 1991, undated
      - Uncorrected printout photocopy (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Inscribed corrected printout (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Photocopied proof (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Printout of Ben Crenshaw's introduction (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - And If You Play Golf You're My Friend, 1994, undated
      - Draft printout (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Partial corrected draft printout with insert (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Inscribed corrected partial printout (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Corrected original settingcopy, with correspondence (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Three color printouts of front cover (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - For All Who Love the Game, 1995, undated
      - Partial corrected draft printout (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Corrected draft printout (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Corrected draft printout photocopy (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Corrected draft printout copy with note [corrections and note by Penick] (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Advance uncorrected reader's proof, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Two dust jackets and front cover printout with bookmark (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Edited photocopy of "A Story by Betty Jameson" (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - The Game for a Lifetime, 1995-1996, undated
      - Early correspondence, table of contents, introduction draft printout (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Forward draft printout (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Draft printout and diskette (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Corrected setting copy (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Second draft printout of audio abridgement, with correspondence (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - The Harvey Penick Reader, 1997
      - Inscribed and corrected setting copy (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Advance uncorrected reader's proof (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Interview cassettes and micro-cassettes, 1991, 1994, undated
      Interviewees
      Interview cassettes: Betty Jameson, Tom Gresham, Mickey Wright, Mary Lena Faulk, John Trimble, Marshall Pengra, Bobby Moncrief, Harris Greenwood, Harris and Ed Turley, Harvey Penick - with notes attached (24-27 June 1991) (5)
      Interview micro-cassettes: Sandra Palmer, Harvey Penick (July 1994, undated) (2), Tinsley Penick, Kathy Whitworth, women talking
    - Interview transcripts (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence to Penick, 1948-1968, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, 1984-1994, undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Book contracts, 1991-2001 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Merchandise contracts, 1992-1996 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2001, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1993-2002 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Little Red Golf Letter: Correspondence, marketing, agreements, 1993-1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Little Red Golf Letter: Issue 2 Vol. 1 to Issue 5 Vol. 2, 1993-1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Videos (scripts, marketing) (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Bestseller lists (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Book reviews and excerpts (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Golf Digest, May 1992, December 1993 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Choice (Japanese magazine), July 1998 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Clippings on Penick, books and merchandise (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Marketing (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Golfsmith marketing (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Golf Digest articles - drafts and correspondence (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Dead Aim, Inc. (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Penick eulogies and funeral service (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Clippings on Penick's death and Crenshaw's master's win (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Simon & Schuster catalogs (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Tournament invitationals (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - General materials (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Anthology, 2003-2008, undated
  This small series contains four drafts of the fiction piece, "How To Live Forever," first published in Land of the Permanent Wave.
  - Land of the Permanent Wave, 2003-2008, undated
    - "How To Live Forever" four draft printouts and diskette (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Proposal, note and photocopied magazine articles for anthology (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Reviews and marketing (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1936-2009, undated
  Two main subseries constitute the Correspondence series: Alphabetical and Chronological. This arrangement reflects Shrake's, in that he filed some of his letters by correspondent, and some by year. Most correspondence in the Alphabetical sub-series are with friends, collaborators, and family members. The Chronological sub-series contains correspondence from a far wider range of addressors, some strangers to Shrake and others intimate friends.
  A name index for the chronological lettersis available in a separate document. See http://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu/research/a-z/shrake.html or ask an archivist to see the document.
  Please note that letters pertaining directly to writing projects are filed with those projects, as that is most often how Shrake filed them. Also note that some folders in this series are access restricted.
  - Alphabetical, 1954-2009, undated
    - Ammons Memorial Clinic members, 1964-1966, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Brammer, Billy Lee, 1963-1970, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Brooks, Stan / Once Upon a Time, 1989-2000, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Cartwright, Gary, 1963-2006, undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Cousins, Maggie, 1963-1986, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Steve, 2001-2007 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Degener, Claire, 1974-1977 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Growald, Dick, 1954-1962, undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Growald, Dick, 1963-1970, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Growald, Dick – postcards, 1972-1993 (Box 102, Folder 1-3)
    - Growald, Dick, 1974-1992 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Growald, Nancy, 1964-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - JADA, circa 1964-1966 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Kendal, Felicity, 2007-2009, undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - King, Larry L., 1965-1969 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - King, Larry L., 1976-1983 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - King, Larry L., 1984-1987 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - King, Larry L., 1988-1989 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - King, Larry L., 1990-1994 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - King, Larry L., 1995 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - King, Larry L., 1996-1997 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - King, Larry L., 1998-1999 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - King, Larry L., 2000-2006, undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Kunik, Anika, 2007-2008, undated (Box 108, Folder 4-5)
    - Lord, Sterling, 1965-1981 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - McCormick, Ken (Doubleday), 1962-1985, undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Milner, Jay, 1960-1998, undated (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Newberg, Esther, 1981-2001, undated (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Richards, Ann, 1973-1987 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Richards, Ann, 1988-1989, undated (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Richards, Ann, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Richards, Ann, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Richards, Ann, 1992-1994 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Richards, Ann, 1995-1997 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Richards, Ann, 1998-2006 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Richards, Ann, undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Richards, Ann family, 2006, undated (Box 110, Folder 4)